# Naheem Adedokun

I am a proficient, smart, goal-driven Javascript developer and team player with over 3 years of development experience with strengths in adaptability and good communication skills. I am a fast learner, recognized expert in teamwork and communicative collaborator. I have strengthened capabilities in critical thinking and pay keen attention to details

6, Asajon Way, Sangotedo-Ajah, Lagos State, Nigeria, NG. +2347065074554 Email:naheemademola21@gmail .com

Github: <a href="https://github.com/">https://github.com/</a> chiefna heem

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Decagon, Lagos — Software Engineer

SEPTEMBER 2021 - Date

- Implemented a MongoDB transfer system API
- Incorporated the MongoDB transactions API to ensure that some database operations either succeed or fail.
- Handled scheduled tasks with MongoDB.
- Collaborated with software teams to alleviate and fix bugs and errors in the company's system
- Exposure to agile methodologies
- Built projects with Nodejs, React.js and Typescript.
- Handled Database Management System with SQL like MySQL, Postgres, or NoSQL databases like MongoDB.

# Hazzy Technologies, Lagos — Full Stack Developer

JANUARY 2021 - JUNE 2021

- A member of a team that developed a web based fashion solution.
- Wrote technical documentation for new software in development.
- Managed state and HTTP requests with Axios and Redux.
- Experience writing unit and integration test.
- Exposure to agile methodologies.
- A member of a team developing, architecting and implementing backend APIs for Book library systems.

# **QEA Software Solutions**, Lagos — Software Developer

JANUARY 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

- A member of a team that provided software solutions.
- Worked with front-end development tools
- Directed software designs and implementations
- Advised clients on software managements and maintenance
- Collaborated with other team members on software best practices
- Used technologies such as Javascript, Nodejs, MongoDB

#### **TECHNOLOGIES**

- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- Javascript
- Typescript
- React
- Postgres
- MySQL
- Redux
- React Hooks
- Nodejs
- Express Framework
- GraphQL
- MongoDB
- Digital Ocean
- Heroku
- Firebase
- Jira
- Version Control with Git and Github.
- Test-Driven Development.

#### **PROJECTS**

## Job Finder App:

A web app that has its functionalities in helping job-seekers easily find their dream jobs for easy application at no cost. Both the employers and the job-seekers are able to manage their jobs in different ways.

**Technologies Used -** React.js, React Hooks, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB

Link: https://jobwebapps.herokuapp.com/api/v1

https://practical-ride-f3e4bb.netlify.app

## **Transfer Service API**

An API contact that that allows users creates accounts with unique identities and manage their account numbers generated at point of registration across their daily transactions

Technologies Used: MongoDB, Nodejs with Express

**Link**: <a href="https://transfer-service-api.herokuapp.com/">https://transfer-service-api.herokuapp.com/</a>

## **Restaurant-Recipe API**

A food-recipe management app that helps its users to manage food recipes. Where a user can create his desired recipes and manage them **Technologies Used -** React.js, Redux.

Link: <a href="https://serene-mountain-63116.herokuapp.com/">https://serene-mountain-63116.herokuapp.com/</a>

# **ECommerce Comfy Web App:**

An e-commerce application for fashion where users can browse through different fashion wears, add to cart, checkout, and make purchases.

Technologies Used - React.js, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, Firebase, Stripe to process payment.

Technologies Used: MongoDB, Javascript, Expressjs, Nodejs, React.

**Link**: <a href="https://comfy-store-api.herokuapp.com/">https://comfy-store-api.herokuapp.com/</a>/
Link: <a href="https://emperor-comfy-store.netlify.app/">https://emperor-comfy-store.netlify.app/</a>

### **EDUCATION**

Obafemi Awolowo University — B.Pharm

MARCH 2013 - APRIL 2018

**Bachelor of Pharmacy(Hons)**